import type { MCQ } from '../../../types'

export const mcqSet13: MCQ[] = [
  {
    "id": 121,
    "question": "Which function is used to convert a date from the serial format to Month-Day-Year format in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "=SERIALTOMDY()",
      "=DATEFORMAT()",
      "=SERIALTODATE()",
      "=TEXT()"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 3
  },
  {
    "id": 122,
    "question": "How can you obtain today's date in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "=CURRENTDATE()",
      "=NOW()",
      "=TODAY()",
      "=GETDATE()"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 123,
    "question": "Which Excel function is used to extract the day of the week from a date?",
    "options": [
      "=WEEKDAY()",
      "=DAYOFWEEK()",
      "=GETDAY()",
      "=EXTRACTWEEKDAY()"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 124,
    "question": "What function can you use to calculate the number of workdays between two given dates in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "=WORKDAYS()",
      "=COUNTWORKDAYS()",
      "=BUSINESSDAYS()",
      "=DAYS()"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 125,
    "question": "Which option allows you to apply formatting to cells that meet specific criteria in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "Format Painter",
      "Data Validation",
      "Conditional Formatting",
      "AutoFormat"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 126,
    "question": "What is the purpose of Data Bars in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "To create bar graphs from data",
      "To represent data using colored bars within cells",
      "To delete data from cells",
      "To insert new rows and columns"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 127,
    "question": "Which option allows you to clear existing Conditional Formatting rules in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "Clear Rules - Manage Rules",
      "Delete Formatting",
      "Reset Formatting",
      "Remove Rules"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 0
  },
  {
    "id": 128,
    "question": "How can you filter data in Excel based on cell icon?",
    "options": [
      "By using the =FILTERICON() function",
      "Through Conditional Formatting",
      "With the Sort and Filter menu",
      "By applying the =ICONFILTER() formula"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 2
  },
  {
    "id": 129,
    "question": "What is the purpose of Icon Sets in Excel?",
    "options": [
      "To insert icons into cells",
      "To represent data using predefined icons based on cell values",
      "To create custom icons for worksheets",
      "To align text with icons"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  },
  {
    "id": 130,
    "question": "How can you quickly analyze data in Excel to generate subtotals?",
    "options": [
      "By using the =QUICKANALYSIS() function",
      "Through the Quick Analysis tool",
      "By applying the =ANALYZEDATA() formula",
      "With the Subtotal Wizard"
    ],
    "correctAnswer": 1
  }
]
